So if you are looking for a job from home here,
especially a job which you can do
part time sitting at your home, then
today's video is going to be very amazing and very
special
for all of you friends because today
in this job opportunity we are going to talk about the job
from home part time job brought by ICC Bank,
where you can apply even
if you have completed your full term here
and everyone is going to be eligible because
if you are a housewife, a
fresher, a student, 12th pass, everyone
can apply here. First of all
we have come to the official website of ICC,
which is ICC Lombard General Insurance,
so basically what is there here, ICC
Bank is giving you an opportunity, can you work
with them now, in
future, as a general insurance agent, so the work that you will have
here is only that of an
insurance agent, you are going to do the work here, let's
talk about it here,
they have clearly mentioned here that
you will not get any kind of  You
don't have to give them investment here, you can apply free of cost here
and you can reduce the free of cost here,
you
can pay on here, so now you
can pay on here 85000 per month commission in every math,
so here you can earn 85000 commission, that much
revenue, that much you will
get payment, the
payment here is fixed, they will not pay you in a particular salary,
these people pay you in commission here, in terms of that
they have clearly told everything here, what is going to be there, so first of all
they have told here why you should do insurance here, by
becoming a partner of ICC people, they have
told that you will work here directly,
with ICC people you are being given working
flexibility, that is, you have to decide whether
you want to reduce 3 hours or 4 hours in the whole day, you will
decide all that,
you will also decide at what timing you have to reduce that,
give it here
You will get the instant insurance policy, which means that
you can directly give insurance to your friends who purchase insurance from you digitally here.
You don't have to pay any paperwork here. Second, there is a team
commission payout relief for sales and everything related to easy digital claims will be done
digitally.
You don't have to pay any paperwork here. So,
they have clearly told here
how much commission you will get and how much you will earn. So
before discussing this, let's talk about who is
eligible. First of all, if
you are above 18 years of age and have completed minimum 10th class
education or have studied minimum 10th class, then
you
can apply here. So, that means everyone who is a
housewife or if you already do
some business or are a
student, everyone can apply here
and everyone will be eligible here.
So if you are already in government job
or doing private job, you all
can apply here, there is no problem.  This is
not going to happen here, if we talk about it,
these people provide it to you on a weekly basis, it will
depend on the insurance as to how much your commission will be here, so the
insurance will be of various types like car
insurance, bike insurance,
health insurance,
so they have told that if you
take a sample premium of Rs.
25000 for some car, then you will be given a commission of 15%
here, so if you take a premium of Rs. 3750 in this case, then you will get a
commission of 15% on it, that is Rs. 225,
if someone takes health insurance of Rs.
15000, then 15% of that will be your
Rs. 2000, and if someone
takes business insurance, then the premium will be Rs. 8000, then
10% of that will be your commission, that will be Rs.
800, so in this way you are going to earn
in commission here because your
commission will be 15 to 10% online average, it can be
more than this as
they have given an example,
thank you for your understanding
in commission and you can also earn here  But you can earn up to 85000 in a monastery
because you can work
with ICC. How to apply here, there are
three steps to apply.
First of all, you have to download their application
and create an account. You have to
upload the documents here.
After uploading the documents, they provide you a POS
certificate.
When you complete their training,
you will be shown direct training videos of
14 overs. When you
complete them, you have to give an exam
which is called POS, Point of
Sales Contact. Only after you
clear the exam, you will get a certificate
sitting at your home and you
can start working here. So the
best thing about it, which I found, is
that you do
not even need to know the story here to give any exam.
You can give their exam sitting at your home
and you can do everything from your phone. So,
even the laptop is not going to be retired here.
If you only have
your mobile phone here, then you can do it on mobile.  You
can work from the phone, so friends, if you have
any doubt regarding this, then you
can ask in the comment, I will clear all your doubts regarding I Bill Try Me
Best,
apart from that, you can also see here that
many people are already doing
testing with them, we have mentioned here
what they have to say about this company,
people from all over India are
applying here and working,
see, there is a candidate from Jammu, another
from Rajasthan, let's say
from Kota, Rajasthan, from Nashik,
after that from Jabalpur, so people from all over India are
applying here and working,
so if you are also interested, then definitely
apply, I have given you the link to
apply in the description,
you can apply from there and if you have any doubt, then
ask in the comment box regarding I Bill Try Me Best, your
doubts should be cleared, apart from that, we will
meet you tomorrow in a new video
with new updates, till then  Goodbye friends